<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>A Simple Website on Dynamite Pond</title>
    <link>//dynamitepond.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in A Simple Website on Dynamite Pond</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 13:01:43 +1300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//dynamitepond.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Apropos sharing with the world</title>
      <link>//dynamitepond.com/article/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 13:01:43 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//dynamitepond.com/article/first/</guid>
      <description>At some point, everyone has something they want to say. The challenge is knowing how to say it, and who to say it to. Family, friends, colleagues - they are all viable and perhaps necessary outlets for pent up genius. But can you trust them? Will they listen? Will they even understand? Are they below you, or do they consider themselves superior?
Fortunately for those in a quandary the internet provides a soothing regurgitant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>//dynamitepond.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//dynamitepond.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Dynamite Pond is a static website generated using Hugo and hosted on GitHub Pages. It is designed to be minimal and easy to navigate.
Layout and style The layout has been kept very simple, to improve compatibility with many devices. The styling is also minimal, no animations or pop-ups to frustrate a reader with delays and hiding menus.
Advertising At the moment there are no advertisements built into this site, and I will never include any javascript/markup from a third party advertising company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>//dynamitepond.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//dynamitepond.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>If you have any comments, questions, feedback, or anything else, please compose an email and send it to:
contact@dynamitepond.com</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>